We will return for your decision
the day after tomorrow.
Will that be all right, Mr. Sebas?
Going out?
--Yeah.
--Do you have any money?
No, but if I need to, I can sell an item--
Take that.
Thanks. I'll take it.
Yo, virgin!
It has been too long, Lady Gagaran.
Er, I mean, Miss Gagaran.
Yeah.
And you, too, Lady Evileye.
Long time no see.
What's up, you here to get lucky with me?
No, not that.
Lady Aindra is visiting Princess Renner,
and she asked me to give you a message.
Hmm? Lakyus did?
Yes. She says, "We're going to be
going into action on the double.
I want you to get ready
to go into battle at a moment's notice."
Okay, but you went to a lot
of trouble for such a minor chore.
Not at all. Also, I was fortunate enough
to have Lord Stronoff
train me in swordsmanship.
He complimented me on that
strike from above that you taught me.
Oh, that? No kidding? Nice going!
--Even so...
--I know. I will not become complacent,
and wish to devote myself to further training.
That's good and all, but I figure
that move could be countered.
It's time you came up with
another move you can transition to.
Oh, Lord Stronoff told me the same thing.
I'll bet. Come to think of it, you asked
Evileye for something, too, right?
Magic training, was it?
Yes.
Kid, you don't have the talent.
Direct your efforts elsewhere.
You don't seem convinced.
Those who possess talent
have it from the outset.
Take Gazef Stronoff--he's a good example.
Can you ever catch up
to where he is on effort alone?
I'm not telling you to give up;
just know what you're up against.
Foolishness. Utter foolishness.
Those who chase after an unattainable dream
are certain to ruin themselves.
I am aware of that.
You're the type bound for an early grave.
There are those who will weep for you
when you die, aren't there?
What's this, Evileye?
You've been picking on Climb
because you're worried about him?
Musclehead! Keep your voice down!
Well it's true, isn't it?
First, gain some magic knowledge.
Once you increase your knowledge,
you'll be able to tell what
your magic-using opponents are after.
Then you can take the appropriate actions.
Right.
Climb, don't do anything
to resign your humanity,
just because you want more power.
Huh?
Sure, it's not as though humans
as a species have all that much ability.
In fact, many of the Thirteen Heroes
were species other than human.
Black Knight, the former owner
of the cursed sword Kilineiram,
now wielded by our leader,
had part demonic bloodlines.
Hmm... the cursed sword Kilineiram, huh?
Tell me, is that business about it
having enough black energy
to swallow up a whole nation
when its power is released for real?
Where did you hear that?
Lakyus said it earlier, when she was by herself.
This is the most powerful of dark swords,
created by the concentration
of darkness unbound, all right.
Even with a maiden like me,
in the service of God,
restraining it with all I have,
I still wrestle with it!
Hmm.
Then, another time...
Don't underestimate my dark power,
rooted in blackness!
I will dominate your flesh
and unleash my cursed sword power!
Tonight is the time when your power
is at its greatest, to be sure.
But I will not let you do as you wish,
even if it eats away at my own life!
Ring of the Holy Valkyrie,
grant me your protection!
Hey, Lakyus!
Gah!
I-I'm all right, don't worry!
Hmm, the priestess was embarrassed
to be controlled by a cursed item.
So those pointless armor rings
weren't just for fashion's sake, then?
Princess Renner is in danger.
You two, come with me, right now!
Don't panic!
This isn't something we can do
anything about anytime soon.
Either way, the only thing
that can stop adamantite is adamantite.
Yeah. Hmm? That reminds me of something.
I hear that a third
adamantite class adventurer team
has sprung up in E-Rantel.
What? This is news to me. What's their name?
As I recall, it was Momon.
A warrior known as
the Raven Black Hero is their leader,
and they're a party of two,
along with a magic caster named Nabe.
Huh? Just two of them?
So, what great exploits have they had?
First, they resolved an incident in E-Rantel
where thousands of undead appeared.
Then, they exterminated the
Goblin Tribal Coalition headed northward,
retrieved ultra-rare medicinal herbs
from the Great Forest of Tob,
slayed a gigant basilisk,
as well as defeated a vampire
possessing tremendous power, I hear.
Also, they subjugated the Wise King
of the Forest with their power,
and are keeping him in submission.
That's pretty awesome, isn't it?
You mean, that would be hard,
even for you, Miss Gagaran?
Thousands of undead wouldn't be a problem,
but a gigant basilisk,
with its petrifying gaze and toxic venom?
Without restorative measures,
that would be too much for me.
That is the ultimate foe for a warrior.
I know how strong Blue Rose is.
Miss Gagaran, there is no way you could
be outdone by any newcomers to town!
Whoo! Thanks for the high praise.
--Okay, sleep with me.
--No, I must decline.
See, this is why you're still a virgin!
This idle chit-chat has gone on a bit too long.
We need to go do as Lakyus said
and begin getting ready.
Please do.
--Climb...
--Yes?
That sword on your hip--
that isn't your usual weapon, is it?
No, this is a backup sword.
There's no telling what might happen.
You should always keep a weapon on you.
Also, you have the items I gave you?
Do you mean those bells?
Yes, they are right here.
Good.
Keep three healing potions on you, just in case.
Understood.
You're a bigger mother hen
than I'd have expected.
Stop teasing me.
You punk-ass brat!
You're filthy!
All he did was bump into him.
They're going to kill him like this.
What kind of moves were those?
Hey, old man, what are you trying to pull?
Back off, if you know what's good for you.
Let me through!
Huh? What was that, old man?
I will say it again. Depart from here.
Why, you...!
Shall we keep going?
W-We're sorry!
Hey there!
Are you okay? Shake it off.
You have no broken bones.
I'm going to give you some medicine now.
Here, can you swallow this?
That's it. Nice and slow. Good.
There's nothing to worry about now.
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
Is there something you need?
Who exactly are you?
My name is Climb,
and I am one of this land's soldiers.
Thank you for doing what ordinarily
would have been my job.
It was no bother. Now, I must be going.
Please wait!
If you would not mind, could you
teach me that move you did back there?
How do you mean?
I am trying to improve myself,
so that I can become stronger.
After seeing your outstanding moves,
I was hoping that you might
teach me even a little of your technique.
Hmm, all right, please show me your hands.
Sure.
Thick and firm. Good hands for a warrior.
Oh, no, I am no more than a negligible warrior.
I do not think you need to be modest.
Now, may I see your sword?
Right.
Hmm, is this your backup weapon?
How did you know that?
It has a number of dings in it.
I am embarrassed that you had to see that.
I see. I now have a rudimentary
grasp of your personality.
The hands and weapon are a mirror
which reflects who a warrior is.
You present an extremely favorable impression.
Now, please allow me to ask you a question.
Why do you want to become stronger?
Huh?
A moment ago,
you said you wanted me to train you.
While I credit you as being trustworthy,
I would like to know
the reason why you seek more power.
Well...
Because I am a man.
Ho...
Based on your answer, I have decided
what kind of training to give you.
Thank you very--
However, forgive me for saying so,
but in my view, you have no talent.
Let me be frank.
You might die from this.
It depends upon your heart.
If there is someone precious to you,
you should be fine.
I am ready. Please proceed.
You are confident you will not die, then?
Very well.
All right, I will train you here.
What, right here?
Yes. Please stand ready with your weapon.
Right!
Okay, here we go. Please hold fast to your wits.
Is this the extent of your manhood?
I am still merely getting ready.
Now then, die, if you please!
Congratulations. How does it feel
to overcome the fear of death?
You did well to avoid dying of shock.
That sometimes happens--
A person is prepared to die, and as a result,
they go and abandon their hold on life.
F-Forgive me for asking,
but who are you? What exactly do you...?
I am nothing more than an old man
who simply knows how to handle himself.
For now, anyway.
Now, once again...
Hold on a minute!
An acquaintance of yours?
No.
So then, he is not
an acquaintance of yours, either?
First off, my name is Brain Unglaus.
Please allow me to again apologize
for interrupting you two.
Your name--I recognize it as that of a warrior
who once fought
the royal head warrior toe-to-toe.
So then, what can I do for you?
Wh-What is it?
How... How could you remain standing
with death so close at hand?
I'd like to know. That went beyond
what a normal man could withstand.
That was something not even I--
pardon, someone like me, could bear.
Nonetheless, that wasn't true of you.
You held your own.
How did you do something that great?
I am not sure.
However, it may be because
I was thinking about my mistress.
Mistress?
Yes, I was thinking about
the lady whose service I am in,
and got through it.
That's how...?
Lord Unglaus...
He had enough loyalty
to be able to overcome his fear.
People can muster
an unbelievable amount of power,
if it is for someone who is important to them.
I believe that that is the strength of a person.
If there is something else
that you refuse to concede,
then you can demonstrate a power
beyond what you perceive as yourself.
The only ones I've had, I've already forsaken.
That is all right!
I could do it, and I have no talent.
Knowing you, Lord Unglaus,
you definitely can, too!
You are both kind and strong. Thanks.
I really have been...
Lord Unglaus...
You can drop the "Lord" business.
I'm nobody that a person
such as yourself needs to pay respect to.
Then it would please me
for you to call me Sebas.
Now then, Unglaus, would you and Climb
both mind leaving here at once?
It appears I have some visitors.
Over there, as well.
Who are they?
Those are poisoned.
Climb, watch yourself. They're assassins.
Perhaps I will be in the way,
but I would like to fight, too.
As one who preserves the peace in the capital,
it is only right that I defend its citizens.
In that case, I will help you, too.
Well then, I will take on
those three over there,
so can I ask you two to take on this pair?
--Yes!
Now then, I am afraid that
I will be confronting all of you.
Would you mind not going after
these gentleman on the side?
That was amazing.
Yeah. If anyone claimed Lord Sebas
was the mightiest man in the kingdom,
I'd agree with them.
Even stronger than Lord Stronoff?
We wouldn't stand a chance against him
if we took him on together. Now,
here they come. I'll take the one on the left;
you have the one on the right.
Now then,
I hate to ask,
but would you be the fall guy
who recoups my time spent out of practice?
Oh, so that is what the story is...
You were out of practice.
Then this might be just the thing.
These opponents are perfect
for shaking the rust off.
Don't get in too deep
until you've determined his reach.
Right!
He seems like a fairly benevolent gentleman.
Fright is an important emotion.
However, you cannot be bound by it.
If your physical abilities are not
up to the task, prevail with your heart.
There are times when
the mind outperforms the body.
If by chance, I die here...
please tell Princess Renner...
...please tell Her Highness that I fought well.
Martial Art!
Slash!
Well done.
Nice going, Climb.
Seeing as how they
followed me from the mansion,
I would venture that these are Succulent's men.
What did you do to him?
It is a skill called "Palm of the Puppeteer."
It appears to be working.
Now then, to begin interrogating him.
Eight Fingers is a relatively large
criminal society within the kingdom, right?
Yes it is.
I have heard the name Succulent.
Something about him being one of
the adamantite class Six Arms.
So then, Lord Sebas,
what are you going to do now?
I have made up my mind.
The first thing I will do
is go and bring down the place
that is the source of this trouble.
He says that Succulent will be there, as well.
Best to stamp out any sparks straight away.
Can I ask you two to carry
this bunch to a guardhouse?
Just a moment, please!
Would it be all right if I helped you?
Me, too, please!
While I believe that
Unglaus would fare just fine,
you might find yourself in a bit of peril.
Looking the other way,
just because of the danger,
would prove that I am a man
unfit to serve my mistress.
Then you have made your resolve?
Very well. Then there is
nothing more to be said.
All right, both of you, please assist me.